deepdreamgenerator.com 2019-06-26

# Privacy Policy • Deep Dream Generator

Effective date: April 5, 2017

## General Information

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Deep Dream Generator website. You can register an account which enables you to use Services as defined in Terms and Conditions. The types of personal information collected are: 

## Email Address

Your email address, and any other information you provide are held in strict confidence. We use your email address only for the functionality of the Service, including: 

  * Confirming your identity,
  * Informing you about news concerning the Service,
  * Informing you about changes in the Service,
  * Informing you about changes in Terms and Conditions.

## IP Addresses

IP Addresses are automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page. Your IP address is stored in our user registration database when you register with Deep Dream Generator. IP addresses may be used for various purposes, including: 

  * To diagnose or service technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific company or ISP.
  * To tailor advertising based on geographic area or other information derived from your IP address. Aggregate information derived from IP addresses may also be reported to advertisers.
  * To estimate the total number of users visiting Deep Dream Generator from specific geographical regions.
  * To make sure that people are voting in a fair manner.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. 

You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. 

If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use Deep Dream Generator Services.

Read more here: <https://deepdreamgenerator.com/cookies>.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

We use email addresses for Services. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

When you upload a picture, your picture is not visible to other users by default. You can choose to make it public when you upload it or on a later stage. 

If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Deep Dream Generator does not rent or sell your personal information. 

We never use or share the personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies without your consent except to provide products or services which you have requested. 

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

Deep Dream Generator may update this policy at any time for any reason. If there are any significant changes to how we handle personal information, we will place a prominent notice on our site. 

If you have any other questions about these privacy policies, please send us an email at contact@deepdreamgenerator.com
